这是。
二零二零年海南省初中学业水平考试
英语科试题听力部分。
该部分分为一、二、三、四
四大题。
注意回答听力部分时。
请先将答案标在试卷上。
听力部分结束前，你将有两分钟的时间将你的答案转涂到客观答题卡上。
现在是听力试音时间。
Are you going to do something outdoors?
Yes, I am going on a picnic with my friends.
But if it rains, we'll have to change our plans.
Don't worry. If so, you can come to my house and read some books if you like.
That's great! 1.
听力试音到此结束。
海南省。
二零二零年初中学业水平考试
英语科试题听力部分正式开始。
请看听力部分第一大题：
看图。
听句子：从
五幅图中选择与你所听句子意思相一致的图画，并将答案标在试卷相应位
置。
听这五个句子之前，你将有十秒。
五秒钟的时间，观察试卷中的图画。
听完每一个句子后，你将有五秒钟的时间答题。
每个句子禁读一遍。
1. 2. It's a sunny day.
Let's go out for a picnic.
3. Mom, where are my socks?
I can't find them anywhere.
4. Tony loves playing basketball.
His favorite player is Kobe Bryant.
5. this is Andrews.
May I speak to Mr.
Smith?,B 6.
第一大题到此结束。
第二大题，听句子选答语。
听下面五个句子，每个句子。
此后有一个小题，从题中所给的
三个选项中选出正确的答语，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听每个句子之前，你将有十秒钟的时间回答有关小题和阅。
读下一小题，每个句子读两遍。
You look nice in your new dress.
7. What does your uncle do?
8. Tim, don't run in the classroom.
9. What were you doing at 9 o yesterday evening?
10. I'm going to Sanya with my family on vacation.
三亚
第二大题到此结束。
第三大题：对话理解。
听下面两段对话，每段对话后有两至。
三个小题：根据你所听到的对话内容，从题中所给的
,B Hey, Lucy, nice to meet you.
三个选项中选出正确的答案，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听每段对话之前，你将有二十秒。
中的时间来作答或阅读下面相关小题。
每段对话读两遍。
下面请听第一段对话，作答十一和十二两个小题。
Hi, Peter, nice to meet you too.
Did you go to Tina's birthday party yesterday?
Sure, we had a wonderful time.
Tina's parents prepared lots of food and drinks for us, and we played cards.
It was really interesting.
Wow, sounds great.
Did you prepare any gifts for Of course, everyone did.
I made a model plan for her.
Hey, Lucy, nice to meet you.
Hi, Peter, nice to meet you too.
Did you go to Tina's birthday party yesterday?
Sure, we had a wonderful time.
Tina's prepared lots of food and drinks for us, and we played cards.
It was really interesting.
Wow, sounds great.
Did you prepare any gifts for her?
Of course, everyone did.
I made a model plan for her.
下面请听第二段对话，作答十三。
至十五，三个小题。
Good morning. What's the matter with you?
Good morning, doctor.
I'm feeling terrible.
How long have you been like this?
I'm not sure.
I came to Hainan the day before yesterday.
It's so hot here.
Do you have a headache?
No. I see.
Does it hurt here?
No. How about here?
Ouch. Maybe there's something wrong with your stomach.
What did you eat yesterday?
Oh, my friend invited me to a seafood restaurant.
The seafood was so delicious and I ate a lot.
That must be the problem.
Take this medicine twice a day.
Come to see me in three days if your stomach still hurts.
Thank you so much, doctor.
You are welcome.
Good morning. What's the matter with you?
Good morning, doctor.
I'm feeling terrible.
How long have you been like this?
I'm not sure.
I came to Hainan the day before yesterday.
It's so hot here.
Do you have a headache?
No. I see.
Does it hurt here?
No. How about here?
Ouch. Maybe there's something wrong with your stomach.
What did you eat yesterday?
Oh, my friend invited me to a seafood restaurant.
The seafood was so delicious and I ate a lot.
That must be the problem.
Take this medicine twice a day.
Come to see me in three days if your stomach still hurts.
Thank you so much, doctor.
You are welcome.
第三大题到此结束。
第四大题短文理解。
听下面一段短文，该短文后有。
五个小题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听短文前，你将有二十五秒钟的时间阅读这五个小题。
听完。
然后，每个小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
该短文读两遍。
so much. Thank you She usually wakes up at about 720.
Then she gets dressed and has breakfast.
School days start at 830 in the morning and finish at 330 in the afternoon.
Mary usually goes to school at 750 in the morning.
It takes her about 15 minutes to walk to school.
Her father drives her to school only when it rains.
And she's never late for school.
In Canada, every student must learn French and English.
But Mary doesn't like French.
She likes Chinese.
She thinks Chinese is more interesting than French.
After school, Mary goes to the art club on Wednesday and Friday.
On Thursday, she goes to the park and she practices soccer with other members of the
soccer team there.
In summer, Mary enjoys swimming and riding a bike.
In winter, she likes to go skating.
It's her favorite sport.
Mary is a schoolgirl in Canada.
She usually wakes up at about 720.
Then she gets dressed and has breakfast.
School days start at 830 in the morning and finish at 330 in the afternoon.
Mary usually goes to school at 750 in the morning.
It takes her about 15 minutes to walk to school.
Her father drives her to school only when it rains.
And she's never late for school.
In Canada, every student must learn French and English.
But Mary doesn't like French.
She likes Chinese.
She thinks Chinese is more interesting than French.
After school, Mary goes to the art club on Wednesday and Friday.
On Thursday, she goes to the park and she practices soccer with other members of the
soccer team there.
In summer, Mary enjoys swimming and riding a bike.
In winter, she likes to go skating.
It's her favorite sport.
第四大题到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷中的答案转涂到客观答题卡上。
The
听力部分到此结束。